JEREMY KUTNER

Brooklyn, NY 917-514-9891 jskutner@gmail.com

Senior Product Manager with extensive leadership experience and a track record of successful products and innovation. Demonstrated history working with startups and large enterprise in entertainment, two-sided marketplaces, and video. Proven ability to recognize and capitalize on new opportunities resulting in increased growth.

- Driven self-starter
- Leader and collaborator

- Focus on innovation and problem solving
- Advocate for the user

Experience

2014 - 2019

Sr. Product Manager / Warner Music Group, NY, NY

Artist Services, a shared-services team leading global consumer technology and commercial business

- Generated over \$4mm in direct revenue by leading seven person cross-functional team.
- Cut developer hours by 50% and doubled site visits by architecting successful product roadmap for artist multi-site platform, supporting over 500 sites.
- Generated 3% increase in annual subscriber growth by pioneering new Facebook Messenger marketing strategy.
- Maximized sign-up conversion rates, from 1% to 19%, while slashing testing budget by 80% through internal optimization program.

2019 - 2019 (CONSULTANT)

Product / Maker's Row, Brooklyn, NY

Marketplace for entrepreneurs to connect with industry experts and service providers

- Defined and built a brand new, two-sided marketplace. collaborating with CEO.
- Built product in under four months by breaking down product vision into minimum viable products and an achievable product plan.
- Validated product ideas through customer journey mapping, user persona, and other successful brainstorming exercises with the team.
- Built custom data visualizations for ecommerce KPIs using Google Data Studio.

2009 - 2014

Interactive & Ecommerce Sr. Project Manager /

Atlantic Records, NY, NY

Leading record label of Warner Music Group

- Drove innovation and fostered positivity by mentoring my team of designers, developers and E-commerce marketers.
- Launched unique marketing campaigns across multiple platforms, including web and native apps, games, eBooks.

• Reduced inefficiencies and cost by introducing new standards for agile methodology, lean, and responsive web practices.

2008 - 2009

Project Manager / Next New Networks, NY, NY

Internet video startup, acquired by YouTube

- Increased user engagement and decreased development costs by overhauling custom website platform.
- Delivered a variety of creative marketing and ecommerce projects by collaborating with executive management.

2006 - 2007

Producer / C-SPAN, Washington, DC

• Wrote and copy-edited voice over scripts

Education

2002-2006

B.A. Political Science / Tulane University, New Orleans, LA

cum laude

Product Management Bootcamp / General Assembly, NY, NY
Agile Project Management / NYU, Continuing Ed., NY, NY
Visiting Scholars Program / Columbia University, NY, NY
Washington Semester Journalism Program / American University, Washington, DC

Technical Capabilities

CMS Platforms

- Drupal
- Magento
- Wordpress

Project Management

- Jira
- Trello
- Slack

UX Tools

- Figma
- Photoshop
- InVision
- Miro

Analytics & BI

- Adobe Analytics
- Google Analytics
- Data Studio

A/B Testing

- VWO
- Optimizely
- Hotjar

Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- SQL

Interests

- Coffee and rock-climbing enthusiast
- Passionate about business, marketing, and technology strategy
- Favorite apps: Slack, Audible, Figma, Miro, Ritual
- A keynote speaker at 2018 Chatbot Summit in Berlin and frequent conference panelist